[Music]
But they were a power couple like Jito
and Schwarzenegger
with all the charm and charisma of a
eugenic assist and war crime investor.
But now that the honeymoon's over and
Trump is back on Twitter, he can't help
but wonder if maybe he made the wrong
decision.
Trump took Trump to the chance. Trump
took much of the cleaners, but even that
was still the listener of evil.
Trump did to the dance. Trump took us to
the creators,
but even that was still the
evil.
It must be hard knowing that you're the
reason that your own dreams were dashed.
A cash grab was within his grasp, but
instead he got the
Lord and the character of one of those
offright dudes. He gave him his news and
instead got a loose knuckle. It's a pain
worse than mine
[Music]
to the dance.
so close to the cleaners
but even that was still the lifter of
evil
to the dance
was to the cleaners
but even that was still the rest are to
evil Heat. Heat.
[Music]
They were a power couple like Devito and
Schwarzenegger
with all the charming charisma of a
eugenic assistant war driving investor.
But now that the honeymoon's over and
Trump is back on Twitter, we can't help
but wonder if maybe he made the wrong
decision.
Trump
was to the cleaners.
But even that was still the le of to
[Music]
the dead
of blood to the traitors.
But even that was still the le of tools.
[Music]